Guide to the Steven H. Scheuer Collection of Television Program Scripts
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Wallace, Art 7:14 Appointment with Adventure
8:7
8:10
8:16
14:6 Armstrong Circle Theater
15:5
16:5
18:1
18:7
19:3
19:8
137:5 Goodyear Television Playhouse
172:6 Kaiser Aluminum Hour
365:7 Studio One
417 The Web
Wallace, Robert 164:3 Johnson's Wax Theater
337:8 Schick Television Theater
Wallace, Shirley 342:6 Star Tonight
Wallace, Warren 444:5 Documentary Special
447:2
Waller, Leslie 210:7 Lux Video Theater
Walsh, Henry 196 Lamp Unto My Feet
Walsh, Thomas 376:6 Suspense Theater
Wallsten, Robert 81:1 Danger
227:1 Medallion Theater
255:9 NBC Matinee Theater
257:5
271:5
272:2
272:13
340:9 Star Stage
351:4 Studio One
355:8
382:10 United States Steel Hour
407:4
408:4
Ward, Al C. 76:4 Climax!
Wasserman, Al 338 The Search
Wasserman, Dale 21:5 Armstrong Circle Theater
178:5 Kraft Television Theater
180:1
182:6
186:6
192:3
247:10 NBC Matinee Theater
368:9 Studio One
Waters, Ed 199 The Lineup
Watson, Max 340:1 Star Stage
Watters, George Manker 176:5 Kraft Television Theater
Wayne, Frank 436:9 Entertainment Special
Wear, Ted 144:10 Hallmark Hall of Fame
Webster, Tony 285 Pat Boone Chevy Showroom
Wedlock, Hugh 44 Bob Crosby
151 Jackie Gleason
Weiskopf, Bob 321 Professional Father
379 That's My Boy
Weitzner, Thomas 404:1 United States Steel Hour
Welch, William 421 Wide Wide World
427:6 World Wide '60
Weld, Sylvia 356:5 Studio One
439:9 Drama Special
Welles, Halsted 1:1 ABC Album
1:4
82:2 Danger
84:12
84:13
85:1
85:7
224 The Mask
373:2 Suspense Theater
377:6 Suspicion
Wells, William K. 374:11 Suspense Theater
Wendley, Richard 259:3 NBC Matinee Theater
263:5
265:3
Werris, Snag 151 Jackie Gleason
335 Saturday Night Revue
Werstein, Irving 8:5 Appointment with Adventure
81:4 Danger
West, Elliot 79 Crime Syndicated
377:7 Suspicion
West, Paul 325 Red Skelton
Weston, William 29 Bell and Howell Close-Up!
Whedon, John 187:6 Kraft Television Theater
188:5
211:8 Lux Video Theater
212:5
401:1 United States Steel Hour
White, William Chapman 179:5 Kraft Television Theater
Whitman, Howard 6 American Inventory
Wilber, Carey 9:16 Armstrong Circle Theater
10:4
10:14
174:7
210:1 Lux Video Theater
360:2 Studio One
362:2
370:9
438:11 Drama Special
Wilde, Hagar 69:3 Climax!
70:3
245:5 NBC Matinee Theater
381:12 United States Steel Hour
Wilde, Oscar 261:2 NBC Matinee Theater
341:4 Star Tonight
377:9 Suspicion
397:5 United States Steel Hour
Wilder, Thornton 320:1 Producer's Showcase
342:1 Star Tonight
441:1 Drama Special
Wiley, Carson A. 362:4 Studio One
365:8
Wilk, Max 58:7 Campbell Soundstage
248:2 NBC Matinee Theater
Wilkerson, Martha 162:5 Johnson's Wax
164:1
Williams, Emlyn 225:3 Maurice Evans Productions
Williams, Lawrence 342:8 Star Tonight
Willingham, Calder 313:2 Philco Television Playhouse
313:7
Wilson, Francis 185:3 Kraft Television Theater
Winer, Elihu 4:2 Alcoa Hour
121:5 General Electric Theater
248:6 NBC Matinee Theater
253:8
276:4
Winkler, Harry 122 George Gobel Show
Winston, Jerry 28 Battleline
Winter, Keith 177:6 Kraft Television Theater
250:7 NBC Matinee Theater
Wincelberg, Shimon 94 Eternal Light
227:13 Medallion Theater
Wise, William 103 Frontiers of Faith
376:15 Suspicion
Wishengrad, Morton 10:16 Armstrong Circle Theater
88 Directions
90:8 Elgin Hour
94 Eternal Light
103 Frontiers of Faith
382:10 United States Steel Hour
384:1
401:8
402:3
413:7
441:2 Drama Special
Wolfe, Bernard 170 Justice
314:3 Philco Television Playhouse
Wolff, Perry 443:3 Documentary Special
445:5
Wolfson, Victor 72:4 Climax!
74:3
Woodman, Ruth 10:1 Armstrong Circle Theater
11:1
Woolen, Russel 59 Catholic Hour
Worth, Marvin 343 Steve Allen
415 Washington Square
Yaffe, James 86 Directions
91:2 Elgin Hour
94 Eternal Light
103 Frontiers of Faith
236:9 Moment of Fear
359:3 Studio One
376:15 Suspicion
377:4
385:6 United States Steel Hour
395:2
404:5
405:1
406:5
Yellen, Sherman 364:6 Studio One
Yudkoff, Alvin 14:5 Armstrong Circle Theater
15:1
355:4 Studio One
Yutang, Lin 122 George Gobel Show
Zavin, Ben 84:5 Danger
227:2 Medallion Theater
227:11
227:15
Zelinka, Sidney 151 Jackie Gleason
Zweig, Stefan 438:3 Drama Special
Appendix II: Alphabetical Index of Subjects
Subject listings are followed by box and folder numbers and name of program. For example, "Africa 444:7 Special" refers to a script about Africa stored in box 444, folder 7, filed under the heading "Specials". Likewise, "Allen, Ethan 1:7 Accent" refers to a script concerning Ethan Allen stored in box 1, folder 7, filed with other scripts in the series titled "Accent".
Adenauer, Konrad (interview) 62:15 CBS Reports
Africa 444:7 Special
444:11 Special
446:5 Special
446:12 Special
447:7 Special
Allen, Ethan 1:7 Accent
American History: see "Our American Heritage," "You Are There."
America's Cup Race 442:2 Special
Andersen, Hans Christian 64:19 Chronicle
Anthropology Boxes 1,2 Adventure
278:12 Odyssey
Arab World 442:3 Special
Architecture 87:3 Directions
The Arts Box 59 Catholic Hour
442:13 Special
see also "Camera Three," individual listings.
Astronomy 426:11 Wisdom Series
427:5 World Wide '60
Atomic Energy 446:7,8 Special
447:l Special
Auden, W.H. (interview) 56:28 Camera Three
Automation 29:20 Bell and Howell Close-Up!
444:5 Special
Bach Box 88 Directions
Baird Puppets 86:11 David Brinkley's Journal
Baldwin, James (interview) 444:4 Special
Baseball 427:4 World-Wide '60
Baumann, Cajetan J. B. (architect) 87:3 Directions
Ben-Gurion, David (interview) 443:11 Special
Beyond the Fringe 447:9 Special
Bialik, Chaim Nachman Box 88 Directions
The Bible 87:7 Directions
Biographies see "Biography," and "Portrait."
Birth Control 62:22 CBS Reports
Bolivian Tin 86:14 David Brinkley's Journal
The Bomb 338:2 Science Reporter
447:1 Special
Bourke-White, Margaret 372:10 Sunday Showcase
Brasilia 86:6 David Brinkley's Journal
379:13 Tomorrow
Brando, Marlon (interview) 283:17 Open End
Brazil 61:16 CBS Reports
Breezy Point 442:6 Special
British Guiana 86:1 David Brinkley's Journal
Brown, William (interview) 379:11 Today
Buck, Pearl (interview) 447:14 Special
Burdick, Eugene (interview) 283:17 Open End
Burr, Aaron 1:8 Accent
Caesar 64:17 Chronicle
California 442:8 Special
Cambodia 86:1 David Brinkley's Journal
Cancer 45:14 Breakthrough
61:7 CBS Reports
443:15 Special
Carnegie, Andrew 444:2 Special
Carson, Rachel 62:20 CBS Reports
Casals, Pablo (interview) 497:15 Special
Catholicism Boxes 59-60 Catholic Hour
Cesar (Parisian sculptor) 86:13 David Brinkley's Journal
Chagall, Marc 87:11 Directions
Cherne, Leo 372:8 Sunday Gallery
Chesterton, G.K. Boxes 59-60 The Catholic Hour
Chevalier, Maurice 447:5 Special
Chiang Kai-Shek (interview) 447:16 Special
China 445:1 Special
447:14 Special
Chopin 442:10 Special
Civil Defense 379:11 Today
Civil War 64:8 Chronicle
Comics 278:10 Odyssey
Commager, Henry Steele (interview) 447:17 Special
Common Market 62:5 CBS Reports
Communism 25:9 Background
Boxes 59:60 Catholic Hour
244:2 Nation's Future
372:7 Sunday Gallery
445:1,2 Specials
446:1 Special
447:4 Special
Computers 338:4 The Search
381:5,6 The Twentieth Century
Concentration Camps 442:7 Special
447:13 Special
Conservatism 62:3,4 CBS Reports
Contemporary Living 50:1 Calendar
Conventions (1960) 442:12 Special
Cousins, Norman (interview) 379:11 Today
Coward, Noel 379:12 Today
Credit 86:2 David Brinkley's Journal
Crime 442:13 Special
Cuba 442:9 Special
444:15 Special
Cuban Film-makers 86:11 David Brinkley's Journal
Cuban Refugees 86:8 David Brinkley's Journal
Dada 446:13 Special
Debutantes 442:14 Special
Declaration of the Rights of the Child 447:11 Special
DeGaulle, Charles 43:5 Biography
61:13 CBS Reports
Disarmament 61:18 CBS Reports
Djojohadikusumo, Dr. Sumitro (interview) 165:10 Journey
to Understanding
Dobie, J. Frank (interview) 1:9 Accent
Doren, Mark Van (interview) see heading "Van Doren"
Douglas, William O. (interview) 244:5 Nation's Future
Drought 61:15 CBS Reports
Drug Addiction 443:12 Special
Dulles, Allen 62:6 CBS Reports
East Germany 61:20 CBS Reports
Easter 427:3 World-Wide '60
Eavesdropping 173:2 Kaleidoscope
Economics 6:3 American Inventory
Education 244:3 Nation's Future
285:11 Outlook
433:13 Youth Wants to Know
443:1 Special
444:14 Special
Egyptian Book of the Dead 278:8 Odyssey
Eisenhower (interview) 62:14 CBS Reports
The Elderly 446:6 Special
446:9 Special
Ellington, Duke (interview) 446:4 Special
England 1:5,6 Accent
Boxes 59-60 Catholic Hour
61:11 CBS Reports
86:15 David Brinkley's Journal
444:8 Special
Englund, Roger (interview) 283:17 Open End
Espionage 86:19 David Brinkley's Journal
Europe 62:5 CBS Reports
Exman, Eugene (interview) 447:18 Special
The Eye 278:13 Odyssey
Farm Policy 244:7 Nation's Future
The Fifties 443:2 Special
Finklestein, Louis (interview) 447:19 Special
The First Lady 443:3 Special
Foreign Policy 244:5 Nation's Future
Foreign TV Commercials 86:2 David Brinkley's Journal
Fosdick, Harry Emerson (interview) 447:18 Special
France and the French 64:16 Chronicle
Freeman, Orville (interview) 244:7 Nation's Future
Gambling 62:18 CBS Reports
86:15 David Brinkley's Journal
Germany 61:20 CBS Reports
62:15 CBS Reports
446:14 Special
451:7 Special (oversize)
Gettysburg Address 283:18 Our American Heritage
Gleason, Jackie (interview) 283:16 Open End
Glenn, John (interview) 86:16 David Brinkley's Journal
Goldwater, Barry (interview) 62:4 CBS Reports
Government 329:10 Report on Washington
338:5 See It Now
447:3 Special
Grant, U.S. 446:15 Special
Greece 443:5 Special
445:5 Special
Guardini, Romano 87 Directions
Halevi, Jehuda (Yudah ha-Levi) 88:6 Directions
Halpern, Seymour (interview) 379:11 Today
Hamilton, Alexander 1:8 Accent
Harlem 62:21 CBS Reports
Harriman, Averell (interview) 372:8 Sunday Gallery
Hermit (interview) 86:10 David Brinkley's Journal
Hickenlooper, Bourke B. (interview) 244:7 Nation's Future
History (general)
see "Accent," "Camera Three," "Catholic Hour," "Chronicle," "Our American Heritage," and "You Are There,"
(individual listings).
History (Western) 1:9 Accent
Hitler 446:14 Special
451:7 Special (oversize)
Hoffman, Paul Gray (interview) 372:8 Sunday Gallery
Hollywood 443:6 Special
Hong Kong 443:7 Special
446:10 Special
Hoover, Herbert 447:20 Special
Houses and Homes 443:8 Special
Human Rights 442:17 Special
445:11 Special
Hypnosis 381:9 Understanding Our World
Indonesia 165:10 Journey to Understanding
Interviews: listed separately at end
Iran 61:3 CBS Reports
Israel Box 88 Directions
443:11 Special
Italy 381:8 Twentieth Century
Jazz 6:5 All About Music
86:5 David Brinkley's Journal
97:6 Excursion
430:4 You Are There
446:4 Special
Journalism 415 WCBS-TV Views the Press
62:1 CBS Reports
Judaism Boxes 86,87 Directions
Juvenile Delinquency 447:10 Special
Kariba Dam 447:7 Special
Kaufmann, George 446:13 Special
Khan, Aly (interview) 444:13 Special
King, Martin Luther Jr. (interview) 444:4 Special
Knox, Ronald Box 59 Catholic Hour
Labor 86:9 David Brinkley's Journal
338:9 Seven Lively Arts
443:9 Special
443:13 Special
444:8 Special
Lamborene, Gabon 443:14 Special
Land Scandals 86:18 David Brinkley's Journal
Lapp, Ralph (interview) 379:11 Today
Latin America 442:4 Special
Lehman, Herbert H. 87:12 Directions
Lincoln, Abe 62:2 CBS Reports
283:18 Our American Heritage
Lindbergh 86:7 David Brinkley's Journal
Linnaeus 6:2 American Inventory
Lippman, Walter (interview) 61:19 CBS Reports
62:8 CBS Reports
Literature Box 338 Seven Lively Arts
see also "Camera Three," individual listings.
MacLeish, Archibald (interview) 447:21 Special
Madrigals 88:1 Directions
Man of the Year 443:16 Special
Mao-Tse-Tung 43:3 Biography
Marriage and the Family Box 59 The Catholic Hour
Mason, Lowell 87:9 Directions
Mathematics 225:1 Mathematics
Mather, Kirtley (interview) 244:6 Nation's Future
May, Rollo (interview) 244:6 Nation's Future
McCarthy, Eugene (interview) 244:6 Nation's Future
McCluskey, Neil (interview) 244:3 Nation's Future
McNealy, Martin (interview) 244:2 Nation's Futute
Medicine
see "Breakthrough," March of Medicine," "A Question of Life," "The Search."
Mental Illness 45:15 Breakthrough
Middle Ages 278:7 Odyssey
Migrant Workers 61:8 CBS Reports
442:17 Special
Missionaries 87:5 Directions
Missle Race 427:1 World Wide '60
Montgomery, Field Marshall (interview) 447:22 Special
Monuments 86:11 David Brinkley's Journal
Moses, Robert 62:19 CBS Reports
Moses, Robert (interview) 426:10 Wisdom Series
Motels 86:12 David Brinkley's Journal
Movie Magazines 86:13 David Brinkley's Journal
Music see "Camera Three," "New York Philharmonic," "Directions," "All About Music."
Mussolini 445:4 Special
NATO 451:6 Special (oversize)
Nazism 442:16 Special
Nevins, Allan (interview) 447:17 Special
New York City 442:6 Special
443:10 Special
446:3 Special
446:6 Special
446:16 Special
Newman, Cardinal Box 59 Catholic Hour
Nigeria 444:7 Special
Parker, W.H. 244:4 Nation's Future
Parochial Schools 86:24 Directions
Pasternak, Boris 87:3 Directions
Peace Corps 444:10,11 Special
Peerce, Jan 87:13 Directions
Pfeffer, Leo (interview) 244:3 Nation's Future
Picasso 444:9 Special
Poetry 88:4 Directions
see also "Camera Three," individual listings.
Politics 61:9,10 CBS Reports
329:10 Report on Washington
338:5 See It Now
442:12 Special
446:16 Special
see also "Camera Three," and "CBS Reports," individual listings.
The Poor 446:6 Special
Population Explosion 61:2 CBS Reports
61:5 CBS Reports
The Postal System Box 223 The Mail Story
Prejudice: see heading "Race and Predjudice."
The Presidency 447:3 Special
The Press: see heading "Journalism."
Protestant Church Box 87 Directions
Puerto Ricans 446:3 Special
Race and Prejudice 29:19 Bell and Howell Close-Up!
Box 59 The Catholic Hour
88:8 Directions
88:12 Directions
442:11 Special
(and Jews) 442:16 Special
444:3 Special
444:4 Special
(and Jews) 445:3 Special
Religion 244:6 Nation's Future
see also "Catholic Hour," "Directions," "Eternal Light," "Frontiers of Faith," "Lamp Unto My Feet," "Look Up and Live."
The Renaissance 335:5 Saga of Western Man
Rhodesia 446:12 Special
Rock and Roll 86:3 David Brinkley's Journal
Rockne, Knute 433:12 You Asked for It
Rodeo 444:12 Special
Rogers, Will 43:2 Biography
Rome 278:11 Odyssey
Roosevelt, James A. (interview) 244:2 Nation's Future
Roosevelt, Theodore 43:1 Biography
Royalty 447:2 Special
Rusk, Dean (interview) 62:10 CBS Reports
329:10 Report on Washington
Russia 278:14 Odyssey
433:13 Youth Wants to Know
446:1 Special
Sacco and Vanzetti 445:6 Special
St. Patrick 446:2 Special
St. Tropez 86:17 David Brinkley's Journal
Salem Witch Trials 278:6 Odyssey
Salk, Jonas (interview) 447:23 Special
Sandburg, Carl 61:12 CBS Reports
School Prayer Case 62:2 CBS Reports
Schwartz, Harry (interview) 372:8 Sunday Gallery
Schweitzer, Albert 443:14 Special
Science and Technology
see "Adventure," "American Inventory," "The Search," "Science Reporter," and "Wisdom Series."
Scott, Robert F. 278:9 Odyssey
Shakespeare 281:9 Omnibus
445:10 Special
The plays:
225:6 Maurice Evans Productions
Taming of the Shrew
279:6 Omnibus
King Lear
281:3 Omnibus
Hamlet
309:8 Philco Playhouse
Othello
360:4 Studio One
Julius Caesar
438:10 Special
Hamlet
Shapley, Harlow (interview) 426:11 Wisdom Series
Shaw, G.B. 446:11 Special
Sloane, Alfred P. (interview) 447:24 Special
Slums 86:3 Davld Brinkley's Journal
Small Towns in America 63:7 Chet Huntley Reporting
Smith, Margaret Shase 61:10 CBS Reports
Smoking 29:4 At Issue
62:9 CBS Reports
South Africa 62:12 CBS Reports
South American Middle Class 86:17 David Brinkley's Journal
Soviet Education 433:13 Youth Wants to Know
Space 61:4 CBS Reports
62:11 CBS Reports
426:11 Wisdom Series
442:1 Special
442:5 Special
445:12 Special
Sudan 446:5 Special
Sunken Treasure 278:5 Odyssey
Supreme Court 62:16,17 CBS Reports
Surveillance 173:2 Kaleidoscope
244:4 Nation's Future
Technology: see "Science and Technology."
Television 6:4 American Inventory
86:2 David Brinkley's Journal
86:13 David Brinkley's Journal
Theater Box 59 Catholic Hour
445:7 Special
Tombstone, Arizona 86:18 David Brinkley's Journal
Toynbee, Arnold (interview) 447:25 Special
Toys 86:19 David Brinkley's Journal
Trade 62:7 CBS Reports
Tratel 6:5 American Inventory
Box 197 Let's Take a Trip
Trawlers 86:10 David Brinkley's Journal
Trujillo 61:6 CBS Reports
Truman 43:4 Biography
Twain, Mark 444:1 Special
UNICEF 445:9 Special
United Nations 372:8 Sunday Gallery
United States 447:3 Special
Van Doren, Mark (interview) 447:21 Special
Vandalia 63:7 Chet Huntley Reporting
Vanzetti, and Sacco 445:6 Special
Venereal Disease 325:2 A Question of Life
Viet Nam 446:17 Special
Virginia City 278:4 Odyssey
War 61:17 CBS Reports
62:13 CBS Reports
Warsaw 447:12 Special
West Virginia 86:12 David Brinkley's Journal
Williams, Edward Bennett (interview) 244:4 Nation's Future
Women and Women's Problems Box 324 Purex Special for Women
World War I 443:4 Special
447:12 Special
World War II Box 29 Battleline
207:3 Look Up and Live
381:7 Twentieth Century
Box 415 Victory at Sea
442:7 Special
445:3,4 Special
447:8 Special
447:13 Special
Wright, Frank Lloyd (interview) 447:26 Special
X, Malcolm (interview) 44:4 Special
Yarmolinsky, Adam 379:11 Today
Youth 445:8 Special
Appendix III: Alphabetical Index of Interview Subjects
Interview subject listings are followed by box and folder numbers and name of program. For example, "Adenauer, Konrad 62:15 CBS Reports" refers to a interview with Konrad Adenauer stored in box 62, folder 15, filed with other programs broadcast under the title "CBS Reports".
Adenauer, Konrad 62:15 CBS Reports
Auden, W.H. 56:28 Camera Three
Baldwin, James 444:4 Special
Ben-Gurion, David 443:11 Special
Brando, Marlon 283:17 Open End
Brown, William 379:11 Today
Buck, Pearl 447:14 Special
Burdick, Eugene 283:17 Open End
Casals, Pablo 447:15 Special
Cherne, Leo 372:8 Sunday Gallery
Chiang Kai-Shek 447:16 Special
Commager, Henry Steele 447:17 Special
Cousins, Norman 379:11 Today
Djojohadikusumo, Dr. Sumitro 165:10 Journey to Understanding
Dobie, J. Frank 1:9 Accent
Douglas, William O. 244:5 Nation's Future
Eisenhower, Dwight D. 61:14 CBS Reports
62:14 CBS Reports
Ellington, Duke 446:4 Special
Englund, Roger 283:17 Open End
Exman, Eugene 447:18 Special
Finklestein, Louis 447:19 Special
Foley, Madeline 447:15 Special
Fosdick, Harry Emerson 447:18 Special
Freeman, Orville 244:7 Nation's Future
Gleason, Jackie 283:16 Open End
Glenn, John 86:16 David Brinkley's Journal
Goldwater, Barry 62:4 CBS Reports
Halpern, Seymour 379:11 Today
Harrinan, Averell 372:8 Sunday Gallery
Hermit 86:10 David Brinkley's Journal
Hickenlooper, Bourke B. 244:7 Nation's Future
Hoffman, Paul Gray 372:8 Sunday Gallery
Hoover, Herbert 447:20 Special
Khan, Aly 444:13 Special
King, Martin Luther Jr. 444:4 Special
Lapp, Ralph 379:11 Today
Lippmann, Walter 61:19 CBS Reports
62:8 CBS Reports
MacLeish, Archibald 447:21 Special
Mather, Kirtland 244:6 Nation's Future
May, Rollo 244:6 Nation's Future
McCarthy, Eugene 244:6 Nation's Future
McCluskey, Neil 244:3 Nation's Future
McNeally, Martin 244:2 Nation's Future
Montgomery, Field Marshal 447:22 Special
Moses, Robert 426:10 Wisdom Series
Nevins, Allan 447:17 Special
Parker, W.H. 244:4 Nation's Future
Pfeffer, Leo 244:3 Nation's Future
Roosevelt, James A. 244:2 Nation's Future
Rusk, Dean 62:10 CBS Reports
Salk, Jonas 447:23 Special
Schwartz, Harry 372:8 Sunday Gallery
Shapley, Harlow 426:11 Wisdom Series
Sloane, Alfred P. 447:24 Special
Toynbee, Arnold 447:25 Special
Van Doren, Mark 447:21 Special
Williams, Edward Bennet 244:4 Nation's Future
Wright, Frank L. 447:26 Special
X, Malcolm 444:4 Special
Yarmolinski, Adam 379:11 Today
Television programs -- Reviews; Television programs -- United States; Television scripts; Television -- United States; Television scripts; Scheuer, Steven H., 1926-2014; American Broadcasting Company; Columbia Broadcasting System, inc; National Broadcasting Company; TV Key
- ALPHABETICAL LISTING OF SCRIPTS BY PROGRAM TITLES
  Scope and Contents
  Scripts are listed by program title, followed by episode title, date, and author, if known.
  - ABC ALBUM
    TV Drama.
    Producer: Herbert Brodkin
    Director: Ralph Nelson
    - Outlaw's Reckoning #1 Halsted Welles, 1953 Nov 3 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Mister Glencannon Takes All #2 Alvin Sapinsley, n.y. Apr 19 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Sketchbook #7 John Collier, Dorothy Parker, Stephen Vincent Benet, and Saki, n.y. May 24 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - The Turning Point #11 Halsted Welles, n.y. Jun 21 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - ACCENT
    History.
    Producer: Don Kellerman
    Director: John Desmond
    - The Elizabethans: The Country, 1962 Feb 3 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - The Elizabethans: The City, 1962 Feb 10 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Ethan Allen and the Green Mountain Boys, 1962 Feb 17 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Interview at Weehawken Joseph Hurley, 1962 Mar 24 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Interview with J. Frank Dobie, 1962 Mar 31 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - ACCENT ON COMEDY
    Comedy, variety.
    Producer: Abe Burrows
    Director: Abe Burrows and Perry Lafferty
    Writers: George Foster and Jay Burton
    - 1960 Apr 28 (4 copies) (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - ADVENTURE
    American Museum of Natural History. Nature and Anthropology
    Producer: Perry Wolf and Charles Romine
    Director: Allen Reisner
    Writers: Charles Romine, William Templeton, Robert Northshield, Richard McCracken, Shelby Gordon, Frank DeFelitta, and Walter Fairservis
    - 1953 May 31 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 1953 Jun 7 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 1953 Jun 14 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - 1953 Jul 5 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 1953 Aug 2 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 1954 May 9 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - 1956 Feb 5 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - 1956 Mar 4 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - 1956 Mar 17 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - ADVENTURES OF ROBIN HOOD
    Dramatic series
    Oversize.
    - The Mark #11 (Box 451, Folder 1)
  - ALCOA HOUR
    Producers: Herbert Brodkin and Philip Barry
    Directors: Norman Felton, Ralph Nelson, Robert Mulligan, Sidney Lumet, and Daniel Petrie
    - The Expendable House Reginald Rose, 1955 Oct 9 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - The Black Wings Joseph Schull, 1955 Oct 16 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - The Small Servant S. I. Abelow, 1955 Oct 30 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Thunder in Washington David Davidson, 1955 Nov 27 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Undertow Jack Kelsey, 1955 Dec 11 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Tragedy in a Temporary Town Reginald Rose, 1956 Feb 19 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Even the Weariest River Alvin Sapinsley, 1956 Apr 15 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Paris and Mrs. Perlman John Vlahos, 1956 Apr 29 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - President (2 copies) David Davidson, 1956 May 13 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - The Magic Horn Herman Raucher, 1956 Jun 10 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - The Archangel Harrigan Lorenzo Semple, Jr., 1956 Jun 24 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - The Piper of St. James Hugh Kemp, 1956 Jul 8 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Sister Sidney Carroll, 1956 Jul 22 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Kiss and Tell F. Hugh Herbert, 1956 Aug 5 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - The Girl in Chapter One Elihu Winer, 1956 Sep 2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - The Big Wave Pearl Buci, 1956 Sep 30 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - No License to Kill Alvin Boretz, 1957 Feb 3 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - The Big Buildup Roger O. Hirson, 1957 Mar 31 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Nothing to Lose Jerome Ross, 1957 Apr 14 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - The Money Killer Harold Swanton, 1957 Apr 28 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Protege Philo Higley, 1957 May 19 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Mrs. Gilling and the Skyscraper Summer Locke Elliott, 1957 Jun 9 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Awake with Fear David Driscoll, 1957 Jun 23 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - He's for Me Michael Dreyfus Michael Brown, 1957 Jul 21 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - No License to Kill (live repeat; see 3 Feb.) Alvin Boretz, 1957 Sep 1 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Night Bill Barrett, 1957 Sep 22 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - County Fair Time Douglas Taylor, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Dollface Jerome Ross, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - The Sentry John Gay, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)